const questionsAsked = [
  {
    question: 'Typical adult dogs have how many teeth? ',
    choices: ['A) 24', 'B) 38', 'C) 42', 'D) 40'],
    correctAnswer: 'C) 42'
  },
  {
    question: 'Dogs sweat through what part of their body?',
    choices: ['A) Mouth', 'B) Paws', 'C) Eyeballs', 'D) Ears'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Paws'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many weeks after conception are puppies delivered?',
    choices: ['A) 12', 'B) 10', 'C) 9', 'D) 14'],
    correctAnswer: 'C) 9'
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Queen of England's favorite breed?",
    choices: ['A) Corgi', 'B) Poodle', 'C) Pomeranian', 'D) Huskey'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Corgi'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the smallest dog breed?',
    choices: ['A) Dachshund', 'B) Shih Tzu', 'C) Great Dane', 'D) Chihuahua'],
    correctAnswer: 'D) Chihuahua'
  },
  {
    question: "This breed was also known as St. John's Newfoundland.",
    choices: [
      'A) Newfoundland',
      'B) Golden retriever',
      'C) Greyhound',
      'D) Labrador'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'D) Labrador'
  },
  {
    question: 'A dog breed with a black tongue.',
    choices: ['A) Pit Bull', 'B) Dalmatian', 'C) Boder Collie', 'D) Chow Chow'],
    correctAnswer: 'D) Chow Chow'
  },
  {
    question:
      "If it's too hot or too cold for me, it probably is for my dog as well.",
    choices: ['True', 'False', 'Fake News', 'Reality'],
    correctAnswer: 'True'
  },
  {
    question: 'The most popular dog is?',
    choices: ['A) German Shepard', 'B) Labrador', 'C) Huskey', 'D) Golden'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Labrador'
  },
  {
    question:
      "It's cheaper to spay or neuter a dog than to raise its litter of puppies for a year",
    choices: ['True', 'False', 'Fake News', 'Reality'],
    correctAnswer: 'True'
  }
];
